veetle.com 2015-06-23

# Veetle: Connecting your World with Live Video

Last Updated Date: July, 2013

Veetle provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of www.veetle.com, www.veetle.org, and www.veetle.info (collectively and individually, the "Sites"). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Sites. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Sites. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. 

As used in this policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally. 

## Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Sites, services, features and content, to administer registration and correspondence through the Sites (together, the "Service") and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Sites. 

## Personally Identifiable Information.

You have the option of registering with us through the Sites and creating a Veetle account or creating your own profile webpage on the Sites ("Account") and we will ask you for personally identifiable information in this regard. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail, financial account information, and/or physical address. You will also be asked to create a username and password if you create an Account with us. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. Notwithstanding the foregoing, it is possible to use the Sites and Service without creating an Account and if you do not create an Account then we will not ask you to provide us with Personal Information. 

  1. If you choose to become a paying subscriber, we will ask you to provide payment information (which may include Personal Information) such as your full name, credit card number, billing address, zip code, credit card security code, other financial account number for non-credit card billing methods, and/or other information necessary to process and verify your payment. For more information about our paid subscription service, please refer to our Terms of Service. 
  2. We may also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your Account (e.g., without limitation, zip code (on its own), gender (on its own), and individual preferences) ("Non-Identifying Information"). 
  3. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries. 
  4. We also use your Personal Information to contact you with Veetle newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your "user preferences" information. (See "Changing or Deleting Information," below.) 

## Log Data

We may use the Google Analytics service and other similar services (" **Third Party Analytics Services** "), to collect, monitor and analyze information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (" **Log Data** "); this Log Data may include but is not limited to information such as your computer's browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Sites, pages of our Sites that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Sites, access times and dates, and other statistics. Veetle does not collect or record such Log Data, rather the Log Data is made available by such Third Party Analytics Services to Veetle in an aggregate form only and not on an individual user basis. Veetle uses such aggregate Log Data in order to increase the Sites' and Service's functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to our visitors' needs, and to understand and analyze how Veetle users in general are using the Sites or Service. 

## Cookies

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Sites and to identify you when you are actively using the Sites. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Sites and Service and then close your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Sites or all functionality of the Service. 

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Veetle. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request information from you in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission's website.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Your Profile

When you submit your Personal Information to create a profile webpage for your Account, Veetle users will see your screen name. Providing profile information beyond your screen name is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with Veetle users. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and that you not use your real name as your screen name. 

### Service Providers

We may employ or use third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Sites-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Sites' features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Sites and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Veetle cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Veetle or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

### Business Transfers

Veetle may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. 

## Changing or Deleting Your Information

All registered users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us at [info@veetle.com](mailto:info@veetle.com) with a request that we delete your Personal Information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law.

## Security

Veetle is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Veetle transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

## Our Policy Toward Children

The Sites are not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [info@veetle.com](mailto:info@veetle.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

## Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@veetle.com](mailto:info@veetle.com) or at: Veetle, Inc., 543 Bryant St. , Palo Alto, CA 94301, USA .
